x-plane.org 2001-06-03

# x-plane.org - The Web's Community & Source for Laminar Research's X-Plane Flight Simulator

Privacy Statement for x-plane.org

x-plane.org has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: x-plane.org.

We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. 

Our site uses cookies to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.

Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address). The customer's contact information is used to contact the visitor when necessary. Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.

This site contains links to other sites. x-plane.org is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

Public Forums  
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. (*Please elaborate on the security measures that you have in place.)

Choice/Opt-Out  
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the visitor.  
This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service. 

You can send email to webmaster@x-plane.org  
You can visit the following URL: [http://www.x-plane.org/cgi-bin/ubb/ubbmisc.cgi?action=editbio&Browser=&DaysPrune=45&LastLogin=](http://www.x-plane.org/cgi-bin/ubb/ubbmisc.cgi?action=editbio&amp;Browser=&amp;DaysPrune=45&amp;LastLogin=)  

Correct/Update  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided.   
visit <http://www.x-plane.org/cgi-bin/ubb/ubbmisc.cgi?action=setprefs>  

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact 

RISNY.com  
x-plane.org  

This is NOT the commercial, official X-Plane site  
run by [Laminar Research](http://www.laminarresearch.com/), but instead a "3rd party" site.   
© 2000 [RISNY.com](mailto:webmaster@x-plane.org)  
Terms of Use. Privacy Statement.
